Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Inventory of Getty Publications, 1954-2013 and undated IA10020
Institutional Records and Archives
- J. Paul Getty Museum, 1954-2000; 2003-2013,; undated; Series I.
  - The Cultural Commission's Fourth Annual Armand Hammer Award. Los Angeles: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 5)
  - Fredericksen, Burton B., Jiří Frel, and Gillian Wilson, eds.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 11/1983. Malibu: 1983. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 6)
  - Frel, Jiří, and Sandra Knudsen, eds. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 1 (Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 1). Malibu: 1983. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Frel, Jiří and Sandra Morgan, eds. Occasional Papers on Antiquities: Greek Vases Volume 1. Malibu: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 6)
  - Goldner, George R. Master Drawings from the Woodner Collection. Malibu: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 6)
  - Greek Vases from the Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection. An Exhibition at the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 5)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum 1984 Appointment Calendar. Los Angeles: 1983. (Box 2010.IA.01-12)
  - Kren, Thomas, ed.Renaissance Painting in Manuscripts: Treasures from the British Library. New York: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 6)
  - The Legacy of J. Paul Getty from the Fourth Annual Armand Hammer Award. Los Angeles: 1983. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 5)
  - The Legacy of J. Paul Getty. 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 5)
  - Rosen, Jonathan and Arthur Houghton. Archaic Coins: An Exhibition at the J. Paul Getty Museum from the Collection of Jonathan Rosen. Malibu: 1983. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 5)
  - Wilson, Gillian. Selections from the Decorative Arts in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1983., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 6)
  - Frel, Jiří. Death of a Hero. Malibu: 1984., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum 1985 Appointment Calendar. Los Angeles: 1984. (Box 2010.IA.01-12)
  - Looking at Art Through its Basic Elements. Malibu: 1984. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Morgan, Sandra Knudsen, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 12/1984. Malibu: 1984., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Scritti di Storia Dell'Arte in Onore di Federico Zeri. Los Angeles: 1984. (Box 2012.IA.01-36)
    2-volume set. Packaged as boxed set.
    Condition: Box has discoloration on bottom. Looks like mildew but doesn't rub off. Readability not affected.
  - Morgan, Sandra Knudsen, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 13/1985. Malibu: 1985. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Frel, Jiří, and Sandra Knudsen, eds. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 2 (Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 3). Malibu: 1985., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Preziosi-Getz, Pat. Early Cycladic Sculpture: An Introduction. Malibu: 1985., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Von Bothmer, Dietrich. The Amasis Painter and His World: Vase-Painting in Sixth-Century B.C. Athens. Malibu, London, New York: 1985., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Danly, Susan and Weston J. Naef. Edward Weston in Los Angeles: a Catalogue for Exhibitions at the Huntington Library, November 25, 1986-March 29, 1987 and the J. Paul Getty Museum, November 25, 1986-February 1, 1987. Malibu, San Marino: 1986., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Frel, Jiří, and Sandra Knudsen, eds. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 3. Malibu: 1986. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 2.
  - Morgan, Sandra Knudsen, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 14/1986. Malibu: 1986. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 7)
  - Morgan, Sandra, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Collections. Malibu: 1986., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Sasson, Adrian and Gillian Wilson. Decorative Arts: A Handbook of the Collections of the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1986., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Whisper of the Muse: The Original Album and Other Photographs by Julia Margaret Cameron. Catalog of an Exhibition at the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1986., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Belloli, Andrea P. A., ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 15/1987. Malibu: 1987. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Offprint from The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 15/1987. Malibu: 1987. (Box 2017.IA.11-02)
  - Fredericksen, Burton B. Masterpieces of Painting in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Second Edition., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 9)
  - Frel, Jiří, Arthur Houghton, Marion True and Sandra Morgan eds. Ancient Portraits, Volume 1. Malibu: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities.
  - J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Collections and the J. Paul Getty Museum Guide to the Villa and its Gardens. Box Set., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 9)
  - Papers on the Amasis Painter and His World. Colloquium Sponsored by the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities and Symposium Sponsored by the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 8)
  - Belloli, Andrea P.A., and John Harris, eds.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 16/1988. Malibu: 1988. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Clark, Andrew J. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum: Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection, Attic Black-Figured Amphorae, Neck-Amphorae, Kraters, Stamnos, Hydriai, and Fragments of Undetermined Closed Shapes. Fascicule 1 [USA Fascicule 23]. Malibu: 1988. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
    Series: Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum. United States of America; fasc. 23, 25-27, 30-34.
  - Clark, Andrew J. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum: Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection: Attic Black-Figured Oinochoai, Lekythoi, Pyxides, Exaleiptron, Epinetron, Kyathoi, Mastoid Cup, Skyphoi, Cup-Skyphos, Cups, a Fragment of an Undetermined Closed Shape, and Lids from Neck-Amphorae. Fascicule 2 [USA Fascicule 25]. Malibu: 1988. (Box 2012.IA.01-24)
  - Goldman, Paul. Looking at Prints, Drawings and Watercolors: A Guide to Technical Terms. London: 1988. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Goldner, George R. European Drawings 1: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1988. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 9)
  - Hess, Catherine. Italian Maiolica: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1988. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 1988. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Katzenstein, Ranee and Savage-Smith, Emilie. The Leiden Aratea: Ancient Constellations in a Medieval Manuscript. Malibu: 1988. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Koch, Guntram. Roman Funerary Collections: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1988., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Lippincott, Louise. Edvard Munch: Starry Night. Malibu: 1988. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Deiss, Joseph Jay. Herculaneum: Italy's Buried Treasure. Malibu: 1989. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Gilman, Benedicte, ed. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 4. Malibu: 1989. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 5.
  - Harris, John, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 17/1989. Malibu: 1989. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - Csikszentmihalyi, Mihaly and Rick E. Robinson. The Art of Seeing: An Interpretation of the Aesthetic Encounter. Malibu:1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Harris, John, ed. Cyprus: Before the Bronze Age: Art of the Chalcolithic Perio, Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Harris, John, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 18/1990. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - Holtman, Mary, ed.The Vidal Mayor: Feudal Customs of Aragon, An English-Language Excerpt from the Spanish Text. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Jentoft-Nilsen, Marit. R., and A.D. Trendall. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum: South Italian Vases, Apulian Red-Figure. Fascicule 3 [USA Fascicule 26]. Los Angeles: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-24)
  - Koch, Heidemarie. A Hoard of Coins from Eastern Parthia. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Series: Numismatic Notes and Monographs, No. 165.
  - Kren, Thomas, and Roger S. Wieck. The Visions of Tondal: From the Library of Margaret of York. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Marble: Art Historical and Scientific Perspectives on Ancient Sculpture. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Small Bronze Sculpture from the Ancient World: Papers Delivered at a Symposium / Organized by the Departments of Antiquities and Antiquities Conservation and held at the J. Paul Getty Museum, March 16-19, 1989. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Smith, Graham. Disciples of Light: Photographs in the Brewster Album. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Sotheby's. Carpets from the J. Paul Getty Museum. New York: 1990 (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - True, Marion, and Guntram Koch, eds. Roman Funerary Monuments in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 1. Malibu: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 6.
  - Baldwin, Gordon. Looking at Photographs: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Chalcolithic Cyprus. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Harris, John, and Mary Holtman, ed.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 19/1991. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Guide to the Villa and its Gardens. (boxed set) Malibu: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Jentoft-Nilsen, Marit. R., and A.D. Trendall. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum: South Italian Vases, Apulian, Lucanian, Campanian, Sicilian, and Paestan Red-Figure. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Lippincott, Louise. Lawrence Alma Tadema, Spring. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Sassoon, Adrian. Vincennes and Sèvres Porcelain: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - A Thousand Years of the Bible: An Exhibition of Manuscripts From the J. Paul Getty Malibu, and Printed Books from the Department of Special Collections, University Research Library, UCLA. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - True, Marion, ed. Greek Vases in the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 5. Malibu: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 7.
  - Williams, Harold M., Bill Lacy, Stephen D. Rountree, and Richard Meier. The Getty Center: Design Process. Los Angeles: 1991. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Carr, Dawson W. and Mark Leonard. Looking at Paintings: A Guide to Technical Terms. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Goldner, George R. and Lee Hendrix. European Drawings 2, Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Harris, John, and Mary Holtman, eds.The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 20/1992. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - Haworth-Booth, Mark. Camille Silvy: River Seine, France. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
    Series: Getty Museum Studies on Art.
  - Kren, Thomas, ed. Margaret of York, Simon Marmion, and The Visions of Tondal. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - The J. Paul Museum Guide to the Villa and its Gardens. Malibu: 1992. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Spier, Jeffrey. Ancient Gems and Finger Rings: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - Bremer-David, Charissa, Peggy Fogelma, Peter Fusco, and Catherine Hess. Decorative Arts: An Illustrated Summary Catalogue of the Collections of the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Drawings from the J. Paul Getty Museum: Checklist: Catalog of an Exhibition Held at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, May 24-Aug. 8. 1993. New York: 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Drawings from the J. Paul Getty Museum: Checklist: Catalog of an Exhibition Held at the Metropolitan Museum of Art, May 24-Aug. 8. 1993. New York: 1993. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Cohen, David Harris, and Catherine Hess. Looking at European Ceramics: A Guide to Technical Terms. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - The Getty Kouros Colloquium: Athens, 25-27 May 1992 / The J. Paul Getty Museum, Nicholas P. Goulandris Foundation, Museum of Cycladic Art. Greece: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 21/1993. 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum. Pioneers of Landscape Photography: Gustave Le Gray, Carleton E. Watkins: Photographs from the Collection of the J. Paul Getty Museum, Malibu. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Pfrommer, Michael. Metalwork from the Hellenized East: Catalogue of the Collections. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Renger-Patzsch, Albert. Albert Renger-Patzsch: Joy Before the Object. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-20)
  - True, Marion, and Ken Hamma, eds. Studia Varia from the J. Paul Getty Museum, Volume 1. Malibu: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
    Series: Occasional Papers on Antiquities, 8.
  - Brown, Michelle P. Understanding Illuminated Manuscripts: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Getz-Preziosi, Pat. Early Cycladic Sculpture: An Introduction. Malibu: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Harris, John and Mollie Holtman, eds. In Focus: André Kertész: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Series: Part of 3-volume boxed set: In Focus: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Other volumes in set: Laslo Moholy-Nagy (1995), Man Ray (1998).
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 22. Malibu: 1994. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Jentoft-Nilsen, Marit. R., and A.D. Trendall. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Molly and Walter Bariess Collection; Mycenaean, Faience, East Greek, Proto-Corinthian, Corinthian, Laconian, Euboean, Chalcidian, Attic geometric, Attic black-figure, Attic network, Attic black body, Attic black glaze, Apulian, Gnathia, Daunian, Lucanian, Companion, Sicilian, Lead Glaze, and Arretine. Malibu, Ca: 1994. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Kurtz, Donna, ed. Bernard Ashmole: An Autobiography. Malibu: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Marrow, James. H. The Hours of Simon de Varie. Malibu: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Stoneman, Richard, ed. A Literary Companion to Travel in Greece. Malibu: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - True, Marion and Kenneth Hamma, eds. A Passion for Antiquities: Ancient Art from the Collection of Barbara and Lawrence Fleischman. Malibu: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Davies, Martin. Aldus Manutius: Printer and Publisher of Renaissance Venice. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Deiss, Joseph Jay. The Town of Hercules: A Buried Treasure Trove. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Fredericksen, Burton B. Masterpieces of Painting in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 23. Malibu: 1995. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Jaffé, David. The Earl and Countess of Arundel, Renaissance Collectors: an Exhibition at the J. Paul Getty Museum, Malibu: 2 May-1 October 1995. London: 1995. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Jaffé, David. The Earl and Countess of Arundel, Renaissance Collectors: an Exhibition at the J. Paul Getty Museum, Malibu: 2 May-1 October 1995. London: 1995. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Keller, Judith. Walker Evans: The Getty Museum Collection. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Lowenthal, Anne W. Joachim Wtewael: Mars and Venus Surprised by Vulcan. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Museo J. Paul Getty Guia de las colecciones. Malibu: 1995 (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. Alfred Steiglitz: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
    Series: In Focus.
  - Naef, Weston. The J. Paul Getty Museum Handbook of the Photographs Collection. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. László Moholy-Nagy: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Series: Part of 3-volume boxed set: In Focus: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Other volumes in set: Man Ray (1998), Andre Kertesz (1994).
  - Perry, Sarah. If.... Los Angeles: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Perry, Sarah. Y si.... Los Angeles: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Taylor, Alice. Book Arts of Isfahan: Diversity and Identity in Seventeenth-Century Persia. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Thomson, Richard. Edgar Degas: Waiting. Santa Monica: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
  - White, Christopher. Anthony van Dyck: Thomas Howard: The Earl of Arundel. Malibu: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-19)
  - Baldwin, Gordon. Roger Fenton: Pasha and Bayadère. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
    Condition: Book has been creased vertically, but is still usable.
  - Blair, Margot. The Red String. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Dalby, Andrew and Sally Grainger. The Classical Cookbook. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - De Puma, Richard. Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Estruscan Impasto and Bucchero. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Hamma, Kenneth, ed. Alexandria and Alexandrianism: Papers Delivered at a Symposium Organized by the J. Paul Getty Museum and the Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities and Held at the Museum April 22-25, 1993. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Hill, T. L. Morris and the Kingdom of Knoll. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 24. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. Doris Ulmann: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Naef, Weston, ed. Julia Margaret Cameron: Photographs from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Quaderni: Centro di Ricerche Informatiche per i beni Culturali VI. Pisa: 1996. (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
  - Sargentson, C. Merchants and Luxury Markets. London: 1996. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Walsh, John. Jan Steen: The Drawing Lesson. Santa Monica: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
  - Wilson, Gillian, David Harris Cohen, Jean Nérée Ronfort, Jean-Dominique Augarde, and Peter Friess. European Clocks: In the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Bassett, Jane, and Peggy Fogelman. Looking at European Sculpture: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Bremer-David, Charissa. French Tapestries & Textiles in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Carr, Dawson W. Andrea Mantegna: The Adoration of the Magi. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Cassanelli, Roberto, Pier Luigi Ciaparelli, Enrico Colle, and Massimiliano David. Houses and Monuments of Pompeii: The Works of Fausto and Felice Niccolini. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Corpus Vasorum Antiquorum; Molly and Walter Bareiss Collection: Attic Red-Figured Amphorae, Loutrophoros, Pelikai, Stamnos, Psykter, Oinochoai, Lekythoi, Lekanis (lid), Fragments of Undetermined Closed Shapes, and White-Ground Lekythoi; Fascicule 7. Malibu: 1997. (Box 2011.IA.01-06)
  - Cropper, Elizabeth. Pontormo: Portrait of a Halberdier. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. A is for Artist: A Getty Museum Alphabet. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Arti Decorative. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Disegni. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Chefs-ďœuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Arts Décoratifs. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Chefs-ďœuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Dessins. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Decorative Arts. [English edition] Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Decorative Arts. [Japanese edition] Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Drawings. [English edition] Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Drawings. [Japanese edition] Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-03)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Kunstgewerbe. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Cover: Hardcover edition.
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Kunstgewerbe. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
    Cover: Softcover edition.
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Zeichnungen. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Artes Decorativas. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-01)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Dibujos. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections (Japanese edition). Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Greenberg, Mark, ed. Summary Catalogue of European Sculpture in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Harris, John. Where's the Bear: A Look-and-Find book. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-02)
  - Hendrix, Lee and Thea Vignan-Wilberg. An Abcedarium: Illuminated Alphabets from the Court of the Emperor Rudolf II. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
  - Hess, Catherine, and Timothy Husband. European Glass in the J, Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Holtman, Mollie, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Holtman, Mollie, ed. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)
    Cover: Hard-cover edition.
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Antichità. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Manoscritti Miniati. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Capolavori del J. Paul Getty Museum: Dipinti. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
    Cover: Soft-cover edition.
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Chefs-d'œuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Antiquités. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Chefs-d'œuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Manuscrits Enluminés. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Chefs-d'œuvre du J. Paul Getty Museum: Peintures. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Antiquities (Japanese edition). Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Antiquities. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Illuminated Manuscripts (Japanese edition). Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Paintings. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Masterpieces of the J. Paul Getty Museum: Paintings, (Japanese edition). Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Kunst der Antike. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Illuminierte Handschriften. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Meisterwerke im J. Paul Getty Museum: Gemälde. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-14)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Antigüedades. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Manuscritos Iluminados. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - Hudson, Christopher, ed. Obras Maestras del J. Paul Getty Museum: Pinturas. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-13)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum Journal Volume 24/1996. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 1987.IA.04 - 10)
  - Jaffe, David. Summary Catalogue of European Paintings in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-21)
  - Johnson, Dorothy. Jacques-Louis David: The Farewell of Telemachus and Eucharis. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-31)